<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2014 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Don't test these features on VR Standalone Headsets. -->
    <string-array name="disabled_tests">
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.car.CarDockActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.car.CarDockTestActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.deskclock.DeskClockTestsActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.screenpinning.ScreenPinningTestActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.sensors.SignificantMotionTestActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.notifications.ShortcutThrottlingResetActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.vr.VrListenerVerifierActivity</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Override default strings for features that non-handheld devices may not support. -->

    <!-- This specific test is disabling tethering, non-handheld devices may not support tethering and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="disallow_config_tethering_action">
        Configuring tethering and portable hotspots.\n
        NOTE: If the device does not support tethering please pass the test using the green check mark.\n
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disallowing usb file transfers. non-handheld devices may not support usb file transfer features and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="device_owner_disallow_usb_file_transfer_test_info">
            Please press below button to set the \"disallow USB file transfer\" restriction.\n
            If a USB notification appears, open the notification and check that the
            \"Transfer files (MTP)\" and \"Transfer photos (PTP)\" cannot be selected and trigger a
            support message when trying to select them.\n
            NOTE: If the device does not support MTP or PTP please pass the test using the green check mark.\n
            Check if you can mount the device as a USB drive on your desktop computer. The test is
            successful if you cannot mount the device, and files from your phone cannot be
            downloaded through USB.\n
            Please mark the test accordingly.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling the keyguard, non-handheld devices may not support keyguard and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="device_owner_disable_keyguard_test_info">
        NOTE: If the device does not support keyguard please pass the test using the green check mark.\n
        Before running this test, please make sure you have not set any device lockscreen password.\n
        Please press the below button to disable the keyguard. Press the power button on your device to
        switch off the screen. Then press the power button to switch the screen back on and verify that
        no keyguard was shown.\n
        Next, press the button to reenable the keyguard and repeat the above steps, this time verifying that
        a keyguard was shown.\n
        Please mark the test accordingly.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling the status bar, non-handheld devices may not support a status bar and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="device_owner_disable_statusbar_test_info">
        NOTE: If the device does not support a status bar, please pass the test using the green check mark. \n
        Please press the below button to disable the status bar and verify that quick settings, notifications
        and the assist gesture are no longer available.\n
        Next, press the button to reenable the status bar and verify that quick settings, notification
        and the assist gesture are available again.\n
        Please mark the test accordingly.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling keyguard/lock screen notifications, non-handheld devices may not support
    keyguard/lock screen notifciations and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="disallow_keyguard_unredacted_notifications_set_step">
        NOTE: If the device does not support a keyguard or lock screen notifications, please pass the test
        using the green checkmark.\n
        Disallow unredacted notifications when device is locked by turning on the switch below
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling trust agents, non-handheld devices may not support trust agents and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="provisioning_byod_disable_trust_agents_instruction">
        NOTE: If the device does not support trust agents, please mark the test as \"Pass\".\n
        Please press the Go button to go to Settings > Security. Then go to Trusted agents and\n
        check if the agents are shown as disabled by the administrator.
        Then please press Back and mark the test as \"Pass\" or \"Fail\".
    </string>

     <!-- This specific test is disabling keyguard notifications, non-handheld devices may not support keyguard and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="device_admin_disable_notifications_instruction">
        NOTE: If the device does not support a keyguard, please mark the test as \"Pass\".\n
        Please press the Go button to lock the screen. Wait a few seconds to see
        if a notification appears. Expected result is no notifications appear.
        You should be able to see one after unlocking.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling keyguard notifications, non-handheld devices may not support keyguard and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="device_admin_disable_unredacted_notifications_instruction">
        Note: If the device does not support a keyguard, please mark the test as \"Pass"\.\n
        Please press the Go button to lock the screen. Wait a few seconds to see
        if a notification appears. Expected result is a notification appear with
        its content hidden. You should be able to see the content after unlocking.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is setting a lock screen message, non-handheld devices may not support lock scren messages
    and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="lock_screen_info_set_step">
        NOTE: If the device does not support lock screen messages, pass the test using the green checkmark. \n
        Select a lock screen info by setting a non-empty message in the edittext below.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is setting permitted accessibilty features, non-handheld devices may not support accessibility features and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="permitted_accessibility_services_set_step">
        NOTE: If the device does not support accessibility features, please pass the test using the green check mark.\n
        Check that \'Dummy Accessibility service\' is not enabled in Settings and disallow \'Dummy Accessibility service\' from permitted accessibility services by turning on
        the switch below.
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling volume changes via audio settings.
    Non-handheld devices may not support an audio settings page and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="disallow_adjust_volume_action">
        NOTE: If the device does not support an audio settings page, please pass the test using the green checkmark.\n
        Adjusting the volume
    </string>

    <!-- Non-handheld devices may not support a keyguard and this test may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="enterprise_privacy_keyguard_info">
        NOTE: If the device does not support a keyguard, please pass the test using the green checkmark.\n
        Please do the following:\n
        1) Press the Go button to open Settings.\n
        2) Navigate to \"Security\" &gt; \"Screen lock\" and select the first screen lock type that is not \"None\".\n
        3) Use the Back button to return to this page.\n
        4) Lock the device.\n
        5) Verify that on the lock screen, you are not told the device is managed.\n
        6) Unlock the device.\n
        7) Repeat steps (1) through (6) for each screen lock type other than \"None\".
    </string>

    <!-- Non-handheld devices may not support quicksettings and this test may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="enterprise_privacy_quick_settings_info">
        NOTE: If the device does not support quick settings, please pass the test using the green check mark. \n
        Please do the following:\n
        1) Press the Clear Org button.\n
        2) Open and fully expand Quick Settings.\n
        3) Verify that at the bottom of Quick Settings, you are told the device is managed.\n
        4) Close Quick Settings.\n
        5) Press the Set Org button.\n
        6) Open and fully expand Quick Settings.\n
        7) Verify that at the bottom of Quick Settings, you are told the device is managed by \"Foo, Inc.\".\n
        8) Tap on the information.\n
        9) Verify that a dialog informing you about device monitoring opens.\n
        10) Tap the \"Learn more\" link.\n
        11) Verify that a screen informing you what your managing organization can do is shown.\n
        \n
        Use the Back button to return to this page.
    </string>

    <!-- Non-handheld devices may not support quicksettings but still should be able to validate the API via
    the notification section. -->
    <string name="device_owner_network_logging_ui_info">
        Please do the following:\n
        NOTE: If the device does not support quick settings, please only check the notifications section.\n
        1) Open and fully expand Quick Settings.\n
        2) Check that you are told that your device is managed.\n
        3) Close Quick Settings.\n
        4) Enable network logging by tapping on the left button below.\n
        5) Open Quick Settings again. Check that an icon appeared next to the text about device management.\n
        6) Verify that a notification including the same icon popped up, informing you that network logging has been enabled.\n
        7) Tap the notification.\n
        8) Verify that a dialog about device monitoring opens, and informs you about: the name of the app that manages this device, details about the device owner\'s capabilities, and information that the admin has activated network logging and can see all network traffic.\n
        9) Close the dialog.\n
        10) Tap the right button below to disable network logging.\n
        11) Verify that the notification disappeared.\n
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling keyguard's managed device message, 
    non-handheld devices may not support keyguard and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="enterprise_privacy_keyguard_negative_info">
        NOTE: If the device does not support a keyguard, please pass the test using the green checkmark.\n
        Please do the following:\n
        1) Press the Go button to open Settings.\n
        2) Navigate to \"Security\" &gt; \"Screen lock\" and select the first screen lock type that is not \"None\".\n
        3) Use the Back button to return to this page.\n
        4) Lock the device.\n
        5) Verify that on the lock screen, you are not told the device is managed.\n
        6) Unlock the device.\n
        7) Repeat steps (1) through (6) for each screen lock type other than \"None\".
    </string>

    <!-- This specific test is disabling quicksetting's managed device message, 
        non-handheld devices may not support quicksettings and this may effectively be a no-op. -->
    <string name="enterprise_privacy_quick_settings_negative_info">
        NOTE: If the device does not support a Quick Settings, please pass the test using the green checkmark.\n
        Please do the following:\n
        1) Open and fully expand Quick Settings.\n
        2) Verify that at the bottom of Quick Settings, you are not told the device is managed.\n
        3) Close Quick Settings.
    </string>

    </resources>